An-chan, I like your style!
あんちゃん、スタイルいいね!
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It feels like a lot of cleaning.
すごい清掃な感じだよ
It kind of looks like an idol.
なんかアイドルっぽいね
That's often said.
よく言われますね
You'll be told.
言 われるでしょ
Oh, they look like an idol group.
おぉ、アイドルグループに似てる
That's what I'm told.
言われますね
Since we are friends, he sends me pictures and people tell me that we don't look alike.
友達だから写真とか送ってきて 似てないみたいな 言われます
Are you told?
言われる?
That's right.
そうだよね
I can't dance.
ダンスが踊れないんで
ダンスできないんだ
I can't dance.
ダンスできないんですよ
That's right.
そうなんだ
My athletic nerves have advanced to the point where I feel like I can do some things.
なんか できそうな 運動神経が進んだけど
My motor skills are really bad.
運動神経は めちゃくちゃ悪いです
Is that so?
そうなの?
That's fine.
いいですよ
Did you have any club activities?
部活とかやってた?
In club activities, I did vocals with K sound.
部活はK音で ボーカルやってました
I was doing vocals.
ボーカルやってたんだ
So you can sing, right?
じゃあ歌は できるんだね
I also like singing.
歌うのも好きですよね
I like singing, but I also like dancing.
歌うの好きで、でもダンスが あったと
That's right.
そうなんです
I refuse even when I use it.
使うときでも断ってます
Will you come after all?
やっぱり来る?
It's coming.
来ますね
来るよね
I agree.
そうですね
So when I was just hanging out with my friends, I was walking,
だから 普通に友達と遊んでるときに 歩いてて、
When I was playing around in Tokyo, I was scouted.
都 内で遊んでると スカウトされたり
Not interested?
興味ない?
Not really, not really.
ないですね、あんまり
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I guess it's not because I can't dance.
ダンスできないって言うので ないですね
It's kind of clean and cute.
なんか、 清素な感じで 可愛くて
You'll be popular, right?
モテるでしょ
There wasn't much of a confession.
あんま告白とかなかったですね
Oh, isn't it?
あ、 されない?
It wasn't done.
されなかったです
Really?
ほんとに?
Eh, that's not true.
え、そんなことないですよ
Not much, right?
あんまりでしょ
A little first.
ちょっと最初
Well, just a little bit.
まぁ、ちょっと くらいです
Well, it happened for a while after I entered the school,
え、なんか入学して しばらくは あったんですけど、
2nd and 3rd graders are gone.
2、3年生は なくなりました
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
What about your boyfriend?
彼氏は?
He's not there right now.
今はいないですね
Are you not there now?
今はいない?
How much is missing?
どれくらいないの?
About a year and a half.
1年半くらい
There aren't quite a lot of them.
結構いないね
Hey.
ねえ
why?
なんで?
Somehow, the boy I was friends with in high school was only a friend.
なんか、 高校の時に 仲良くしてた男の子は 友達としてしか
As a friend because I can't see you?
見 れなくて 友達として?
That's right.
そうなんですよ
To this day, I feel like no one really clicks with me.
ピンとくる人はいないなって 今に至る感じですね
Does that mean you can't see me as a boyfriend or a man?
彼氏として、男として見れないってこと?
Well, that's true.
まぁ、そうですよね
I totally see you as a friend.
完全に友達として見ちゃってるから
What, did you have sex with that boyfriend?
え、その彼氏とはさ、 エンチしたの?
I did.
しました
Ah, that's what I did.
あ、じゃあしたんだ
But since I specified it, I can see him as a man.
でも、指定してるんだからさ、 一緒に男として見れるん
Isn't it?
じゃない?
I wonder what he would say.
なん て言うんだろうな
If I have a hobby, I end up only talking about it with the people I meet.
趣味とかがあったら 結局、会う人としか話さないんで
I have hobbies and like to go out for fun.
趣 味があって、 普 通に遊びに行ったりとかも するんです
But we'll end up being friends.
けど、 友達で終わります
I don't think I have one either because I have a female friend.
僕も女友達だから 持ってないと思います
Does that mean we're not lovers?
恋人ってわけじゃなくてってこと?
But shall I go?
でも、行っちゃう?
Well, I don't.
は、しないですね
Well, I do have a boyfriend, though?
え、彼氏とはするけど?
I have a boyfriend, but other people have been told to do things with me.
彼氏とはするけど、 その他の人は言われて 私とのことはあって
Masu.
ます
You're invited, aren't you?
誘 われるよね?
There are a few.
ちょっとありますね
I don't have enough money for my husband's marriage.
私、主婚金いいなんで
The other person too.
相 手も
It's cute.
可愛いもんね
It looks like it might be an underground garden.
地下庭とかされそうだね
When I was in high school, it happened a lot.
高校の時、めちゃめちゃありましたね
there were?
あった?
there was.
ありました
Make the mask art longer on purpose so it doesn't fit.
マスクアートをわざと長くして 合わないようにして
Was it a train or something?
電車とかだったこと?
There were trains, and there were also buses.
電車も、あと、 バスもありましたね
It's on the bus.
バスの中だね
It was really scary.
めちゃくちゃ怖かったです
It's scary, isn't it?
怖いよね
It's scary.
怖いですね
I'm not afraid of men, but that's the case.
男性に対して 恐怖心じゃないけど そういうのもあるでしょ
I wish there was an underground garden.
地下庭とかあったら
There are usually underground gardens and lots of older people.
だ いたい地下庭とか 年齢が 結構上の人たちが多くて あ、
It's an uncle.
おじさんね
That's right.
そうなんですよ
It's a little scary when you look at people who are 10 years old.
10年の方見るとちょっと怖いです
on second thoughts.
や っぱり
picture,
え、
So, how long have you been having sex?
じゃあ、 えっちはさ、 どんくらいしてるの?
I haven't done that recently.
最近はしてないですね
Haven't you?
してない?
How long have you not done it?
どのくらいしてない?
I haven't done anything since I broke up with my boyfriend.
彼氏と別れてから 一切してないので
After all, it's been a year and a half.
だって1年半とかじゃん
You mean you haven't done that in that time?
その間してないってこと?
I haven't.
してないです
I haven't done it with anyone else.
他の方とはしてないです
That's a lie.
そりゃ嘘だろ
It's true.
本当です
Really?
本当に?
Eh, don't you feel uncomfortable?
え〜 むらむらしない?
Well, a little.
まあ若干
Wandering around?
ふらふらする?
What do you do when that happens?
そういうときどうしてるの?
Well, I'm already alone.
え〜もうだから 一人で
fault?
あら?
Seriously?
まじで?
I really want to hear it.
めっちゃ聞きたいんだけどさ
But if you listen to it all, it will take about 2 hours.
でも全部聞くと 2時間くらいかかるね
a little bit.
ちょっと
I'll do that next time.
それは次回に して
yes.
はい
I can't stop playing Pocky either.
ちょっと俺も ポッキーが止まらないんだよ
Thank you for your continued support today.
今日はよろしくお願いします
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
Is there such a thing as a static viewing body?
静観体とかある?
Ears and well, yeah.
耳と あと、まあ うん
Well, the areas that many people are already sensitive to are generally weak.
まあいろんな人が もう敏感なとこが 大体弱いです
Huh, what is that?
え、何それ?
I don't dance though.
踊らないんだけど
So, I'm probably more sensitive to something than other people.
で、何か全 多分 他の人より多分 感度高い
Is that so?
そうなの?
Do you like ears?
耳が好きなの?
I feel a little tingly.
ちょっとゾワゾワする
What should I do?
どうする?
Can you touch me like this?
こうやって触られるの?
sensitive?
敏感?
tickles.
くすぐったい
tickles?
くすぐったい?
Because it's smooth.
すべすべだからさ
I want to touch it.
触りたくなっちゃう
Does it look good?
見 えそう?
Please stand up for a moment.
ちょっと立ってみてよ
It's such a great style.
すごいスタイルいいよね
I just want to see your feet.
ちょっと足見たいからさ
Turn it over.
めくってよ
Take a look.
少々見て
Show me your butt too.
ちょっとお尻も見せて
Wow
うわ
amazing.
すごい
This makes me want to touch it.
これ が触りたくなっちゃう
Look this way.
こっち向いて
amazing.
すごい
Well, good luck with this.
さあ、これさあんばんざいして
close.
近い
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Have you ever been licked in the armpit?
脇なめられたことある?
do not have.
ない
A cute one came out.
かわいいの出てきた
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Please look carefully.
ちゃんと見てください
Please raise your leg.
足あげてください
feet?
足?
nice.
いい ね
I'd like to see it from behind as well.
ちょっと後ろからも見たいな
From behind?
後ろから?
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
Get your hands on me and stick your butt out.
手ついて、お尻突き出してくれ
You can roll it yourself.
自分で巻くってくれるんだね
It looks beautiful.
綺麗らしいね
Look this way.
こっち向いて
sexy.
セクシー
Wait, really.
待って、本当に
amazing.
すごい
It's cute, isn't it?
かわいいだろ、てか
I'm almost here.
手前来たよ
Open your legs.
足開いて
Come to the last minute.
ギリギリまで来て
amazing.
すごい
nice.
いい ね
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
Oh no, it's embarrassing.
やだ、恥ずかしい
It's so embarrassing.
めちゃめちゃ恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
You don't look like this.
こんな格好してないもんね
Should I make you do something more embarrassing?
もっと恥ずかしいことさせちゃおうかな
With your hands, through this, with both hands,
手でさ、 こっから通して、 両手で、
yes.
そう
beautiful.
綺麗
Let's take a closer look.
近くで見ちゃおう
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Spread it out more.
もっと広げて
Properly.
ちゃんと
yes.
そう
amazing.
すごい
What do you like?
どこが好き?
What do you like most?
どこが一番好き?
Yes, Oshiri-kun.
そう、おしりくん
That's erotic.
エロいね
I'm watching it while on my butt.
おしりながら見てるよ
Touch my dick.
チンチン触って
It's delicious.
うまいね
I'm watching it while on my butt.
おしりながら見てるよ
good.
うまい